<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <SightsEfficiency.label>sights efficiency</SightsEfficiency.label>
  <SightsEfficiency.description>How good the sights on this weapon are. Quality sights reduce range errors and improve target leading. This is multiplied against the aiming accuracy of the shooter to calculate the amount of range and lead error.\n\nThe final modifier is calculated via this formula:\n(1.5 - aiming accuracy) / aiming efficiency\n\nLead error is calculated by multiplying this factor against total lead distance in cells. Range error is calculated by multiplying it against the total distance to the target divided by 4.</SightsEfficiency.description>

  <ShotSpread.label>spread</ShotSpread.label>
  <ShotSpread.description>Inherent projectile spread. This represents the inherent inaccuracy of the gun and causes random conical deviation that is not influenced by skill.</ShotSpread.description>
  <ShotSpread.formatString>{0}°</ShotSpread.formatString>

  <SwayFactor.label>weapon sway</SwayFactor.label>
  <SwayFactor.description>How difficult the gun is to keep steady. \n\nThe total sway is calculated as:\n(4.5 - shooting accuracy) * weapon sway factor\n\nAiming accuracy influences the sway reduction during aimed shots. For example, at 75% aiming accuracy sway will be reduced to 25%.</SwayFactor.description>


  <!-- Don't do anything, only display information to the player -->

  <Caliber.label>caliber</Caliber.label>
  <Caliber.description>The types of ammo this gun accepts.</Caliber.description>

  <MagazineCapacity.label>magazine capacity</MagazineCapacity.label>
  <MagazineCapacity.description>How many projectiles this weapon's magazine holds and how long it takes to reload it.</MagazineCapacity.description>

  <ammoConsumedPerShotCount.label>ammo consumed per shot</ammoConsumedPerShotCount.label>
  <ammoConsumedPerShotCount.description>How many units of ammunition this gun consumes for each individual shot.\n\nThis applies to guns with multiple barrels that fire simultaneously with each pull of the trigger, or exotic energy weapons that use up different amounts of energy from a power cell.</ammoConsumedPerShotCount.description>


</LanguageData>