<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Charged.label>charge</Charged.label>
  <Charged.description>The charged particle coating disrupts armor and tissue in equal measure.</Charged.description>

  <ChargedAP.label>concentrated charge</ChargedAP.label>
  <ChargedAP.labelShort>conc.</ChargedAP.labelShort>
  <ChargedAP.description>Focuses charged particles around the tip of the core for improved armor penetration at the cost of stopping power.</ChargedAP.description>

  <Ionized.label>ion charge</Ionized.label>
  <Ionized.labelShort>ion</Ionized.labelShort>
  <Ionized.description>Designed to combat mechanoids, the round creates an electrical current on impact, disrupting electronic systems temporarily.</Ionized.description>

  <IncendiaryFuel.label>incendiary</IncendiaryFuel.label>
  <IncendiaryFuel.description>Filled with incendiary agent that ignites after impact.</IncendiaryFuel.description>

  <NapalmFuel.label>jellied chemfuel</NapalmFuel.label>
  <NapalmFuel.description>Highly flammable liquid, burns over time and catches nearby objects on fire.</NapalmFuel.description>

  <JelliedPrometheumFuel.label>jellied prometheum</JelliedPrometheumFuel.label>
  <JelliedPrometheumFuel.description>Advanced pyrophoric compound in gel-form. Self-ignites on contact with air, sticks to skin and seeps into openings, burning even mechanoids.</JelliedPrometheumFuel.description>

  <ThermobaricFuel.label>thermobaric</ThermobaricFuel.label>
  <ThermobaricFuel.description>Filled with high-explosive aerosol that causes a large explosion and ignites flammable materials.</ThermobaricFuel.description>

  <FoamFuel.label>foam</FoamFuel.label>
  <FoamFuel.description>Special round designed for civilian fire-fighting purposes. Filled with fire-retardant foam to suppress fires in a large area.</FoamFuel.description>

  <Antigrain.label>antigrain warhead</Antigrain.label>
  <Antigrain.description>A tiny ultra-tech warhead usually used by spacecraft or glitterworld war machines. Powered by a grain of antimatter, it creates a huge explosion and starts fires around the target.</Antigrain.description>


  <!-- For Vanilla-Friendly Weapons Expansion -->

  <RadiationIonising.label>radioactive (ionising)</RadiationIonising.label>
  <RadiationIonising.labelShort>stone</RadiationIonising.labelShort>
  <RadiationIonising.description>Contains ionising gamma radiation that significantly impairs consciousness, and is a carcinogen.</RadiationIonising.description>


  <!-- For Forsakens -->

  <ForsakenArrow.label>forsaken arrow</ForsakenArrow.label>
  <ForsakenArrow.labelShort>forsaken</ForsakenArrow.labelShort>
  <ForsakenArrow.description>Designed to be fired from a forsaken bow.</ForsakenArrow.description>


  <!-- For Glitter Tech -->

  <Plasma.label>Plasma</Plasma.label>
  <Plasma.labelShort>plasma</Plasma.labelShort>
  <Plasma.description>Highly-energized ionized gas capable of devastating burn effects.</Plasma.description>

  <RailgunSabot.label>Railgun sabot</RailgunSabot.label>
  <RailgunSabot.labelShort>Sabot</RailgunSabot.labelShort>
  <RailgunSabot.description>Uses a discarding sabot to fire an undersized projectile at higher muzzle velocities, greatly improving armor penetration.</RailgunSabot.description>


</LanguageData>